netedgecomputing.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy of NetEdge Computing – Product Development, Distributed Systems & IT Service Provider

**Introduction**

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy sets out the way we deal with personal information (which means data from which you can be identified, including your name, address, e-mail address and the like) that you provide to us, or that we obtain from you. We request you to read it carefully. We may be required to change it from time to time so we also request you to check it from time to time to be aware of the latest version. You may be assured, however, that any amendments to this Policy will continue to be in accordance with the provisions of the Data Protection Act. Any information obtained via this web site, or any other web site controlled by **NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd.** is the sole property of **NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd.** , A - 14, Sector - 7, Noida - 201 301, India. No third party shall be given any rights to it unless required to do the same by law.

To protect your privacy, NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. has based its privacy policy on NCASE (Notice, Consent, Access, Security and Enforcement) principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

**Learn About Your privacy**

**Notice**  
We shall ask you (when we need) information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before downloading free software, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters or joining a limited-access site. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes: 

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. 
  * To help you quickly find software, services or information on NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. corporate or related websites. 
  * To help us create content most relevant to you. 
  * To inform you of product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from NetEdge Group. 

**Consent**  
If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of **NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd.** websites, but you may not be able to access areas that require registration.

If you decide to register, you will be authorized to select the information you want to receive from NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. by subscribing to various services, like electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate to you other offers regarding our products, programs, events or services by e-mail, postal mail, or telephone, you may establish your preferences at the time of registration.

**Access**  
We shall provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time on the website where you have registered. There, you can: 

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us. 
  * Tell us whether you want NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. to send you marketing information, or newsletters or any other specific information pertaining to NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. website, product or services. 
  * Subscribe or cancel subscriptions to electronic newsletters 
  * Remove your registration from our database. 

**Security**  
NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**Enforcement**  
If for some reason you believe NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at [privacy@netedgecomputing.com](mailto:privacy@netedgecomputing.com "NetEdge Computing") and we shall do our best to determine and rectify the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

**Ferquently Asked Questions** :

**Q.1. What personal information do we obtain and how do we obtain it?**  
When you register for a particular service or offering we ask you to provide the personal information that we require in order to provide the information requested in accordance with our usual operating procedures and quality standards. 

We may also, from time to time, ask you for, or enable you to provide, additional information so that we can improve our service to you or make your visits to our site more rewarding. There will be no obligation on you to provide this information.

We may also use 'cookies', or other forms of information software, to obtain information from visitors to our sites, which allows us to improve the experience of visitors to our web site. You should, if you wish, be able to prevent the use of this software or 'cookies' by changing the setting on your browser, however if you do so, some functionality may be lost. 

**Q.2. What use do we make of personal information?**   
We do not sell, trade or rent your information to other parties unless we have your consent for the same. If we have the permission, we may share the information with select organizations that we believe to be reputable. We may provide statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information, but without disclosing any personal information. 

Your personal information will be used only for the purposes of communicating with you as an individual in relation to our products and services, or for any other purposes to which you have given your consent. 

**Q.3. How do we protect your personal information?**   
We use all reasonable endeavors to protect personal information from loss, misuse or alteration, and have appropriate security measures in place to assist us do so. Only authorized employees, who are under appropriate confidentiality obligations, will have access to your personal information. However, you will be responsible for, and must take all due care to protect, any user ID or password that we have provided for your use on our web sites. 

**Q.4. How can you amend your personal information, or ask us to remove it or cease using it for direct marketing purposes?**   
This can be done at any time by emailing us at [privacy@netedgecomputing.com](mailto:privacy@netedgecomputing.com "NetEdge Computing") or in writing to the person whom the NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. has nominated as its representative for the purpose of the Data Protection, Anusha Saxena at the address of NetEdge Computing Solutions Pvt. Ltd. set out above. 

Additionally we have provided you with the means on the website itself to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at anytime.
